Guilherme Hebling

Front-End Web Developer

📞 +47 925 18 761 | 🕈 0368 Oslo, Norway | 🔀 gdhebling@outlook.com

SUMMARY

Committed Front-End Web Developer with a strong aesthetic sense, attention to detail, and an eye for design. Previous work experience within Business and Marketing positions, which taught me how to collaborate in a team environment with different people from various backgrounds and provided me a good understanding of a business environment.

SKILLS

Web Technologies: Programming Language: Design:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript Figma, Adobe XD

Sass/SCSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind

Web Server: Version Control: Tools:

Firebase, Google Cloud Platform Git, GitHub VS Code, Chrome Dev Tool

PROJECTS

Amazon Clone

Web application created with **React** and deployed using **Google Firebase**.

React Router for UI, React Context API for basket, user authentication, and payment functionality with Stripe.

Deployed Website | GitHub Repository

Photographer Portfolio

Responsive web design coded from scratch using **SCSS** and extensive use of **Flexbox** for the user interface, and JavaScript for responsive navbar and hamburger menu.

Designed the website mockup using **Figma** before the actual coding.

Deployed Website | **GitHub Repository**

Google Maps Store Locator

A website with search functionality integrated with the Google Maps API.

Search input looks for **JSON** list of stores and returns the filtered results on the map.

Deployed Website | GitHub Repository

Tech Company Website

Clean and modern website developed using Tailwind CSS (CSS Framework).

The inspiration for the design comes from tech-related startups and companies.

Deployed Website | **GitHub Repository**

EDUCATION

Web Development

Johns Hopkins University (via Coursera)

HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Web Developers.

A well-rounded course teaching the basic tools to become a Web Developer. Some of the topics included:

- HTML5, CSS3, Responsive Design, Bootstrap
- JavaScript, Web Applications, DOM Manipulation, Ajax basics.

Introduction to User Experience Design

Georgia Institute of Technology (via Coursera)

Introduction to User Experience (UX) Design

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

2011 - 2017

Federal University of São Carlos (UFSCar)

Sorocaba - Brazil

• Professional focus on business administration.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer / Self-Employed

02.2018 - present

Hebling Media

Oslo – Norway

- Web design and web management for local companies
- Assignments as a photographer and videographer on commercial work and the wedding industry

Marketing Specialist 02.2017 - 02.2018

Market Phone Sorocaba – Brazil

- Marketing and customer relations on both online and offline platforms
- Customer service and daily operations

Digital Marketing 11.2015 – 05.2016

Beleza na Web Sao Paulo – Brazil

- Largest e-commerce company for beauty products in Latin America
- Improved website's SEM through Google AdWords and Facebook Ads

OTHER

Languages Portuguese: Native

English: Fluent both oral and written

Norwegian: Very good skills both oral and written (Level **B2** at Folkeuniversitetet - *d.d.*)

Spanish: Good skills both oral and written **Italian:** Basic skills both oral and written

IT Experienced user of Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word)

Advanced user of creative software such as **Lightroom**, **Premiere**, **Photoshop**Knowledge of **MS Access**, **SharePoint**, **CorelDRAW**, **Adobe XD**, **InDesign**, **VS Code**